[MUSIC PLAYING]
Polymer，Rob Dodson
Hey there, Polycasters.
欢迎来到Polycast的老板Rob
Many of you have written in and asked for an episode
你们中的许多人向我们发送了自定义循环的请求
on the Iron Ajax element.
对于Iron Ajax组件。
There's a lot of questions around this element,
许多问题围绕这个要素展开，
like when to use it and is it bad to mix your behavior
就像可以使用时一样，融合风格是否不好
with markup like that.
有了这样的编解码器。
But in fact, Iron Ajax is one of the most useful elements
但实际上，铁阿贾克斯是有用的成分
you can have in your toolbox.
您可以在工具箱中获取。
However, its utility only becomes apparent
仅显示其有用性
when you combine it with data bindings.
与数据链接结合使用时。
Anyway, today on Polycast, I'm going
全天候在Polycast中
to show you the power of working with Ajax
我将向您介绍Ajax的工作人员
using nothing but HTML.
仅使用HTML
Let's check it out.
让我们看看吧。知道了
OK.
所以今天我们将设计一个元素
fetches GitHub issues, and we're going
要查找GitHub问题，
to use Iron Ajax to do that.
我们将使用Iron Ajax来做到这一点。
Now, I'm also going to use the Yeoman generator to scaffold
现在，我还将使用Yeoman构造函数来支持该元素
out my element, but if you don't want to use Yeoman,
但是如果您不想使用Yeoman，
you could use the seed-element project, which I will
您可以使用元素项目，
link to down in the show notes.
我将在下面的视频说明中链接到该视频。
That will do the exact same thing as Yeoman.
这与Yeoman一样。
Yeoman just goes a step further and it
但是Yeoman正在做额外的工作
renames all the files for me, which is pretty convenient.
代表我重命名所有文件，这很有用。
So from my command line, I'll type yo polymer:l-- or sorry,
在命令行上，我要写聚合物：l--对不起
yo polymer:seed gh-issues to generate my element.
yo聚合物：为gh-issues种子创建我的物品。
And once that's generated, I can run polyserve,
创建完成后，我可以运行polyserve，
which is our little local server,
这是我们的本地服务器，
and that'll let me preview the element as I'm developing it.
这将使我在创建项目时浏览它。
And you'll see here that it generates this URL
在这里，您会看到它创建了此URL
that I can use to actually go look
我用来打开
at my element's documentation.
关闭我的物品。
So using the seed-element, it actually
因此，使用初始元素，
generates docs for us, which is pretty cool.
它将创建好的文档。
It also has this demo link here, which we can click on,
这里还有一个演示链接，我们可以单击
and that is going to show us sort
介绍我们
of a demo of the boilerplate element that it has created.
生成的样板元素的演示。
So this is all just stuff that it has sort of stubbed out,
因此，这一切都被截断了，
and we're going to replace all this in just a second.
我们将在一秒钟内将其全部替换。
Now, I mentioned, we're going to use
我刚才提到我们将使用
the GitHub API to fetch issues.
GitHub API出现问题。
So going and looking at the API docs,
因此，当您查看API文档时，
I can go down to the Issues section,
我可以去问题部分
and you'll see here that working with the GitHub API
在这里，您将看到使用GitHub API的工作非常简单。
We just use get request to fetch the issues
我们只会使用get请求来解决问题
for either-- like, all the issues that
对于每个问题
are owned by a user or all the issues in a given organization.
用户或特定组织中的所有问题。
In our case, what we're going to do
就我们而言，我们将要做的是
is we're going to fetch all the issues
如果我们要解决所有问题
for a particular repository.
自己的仓库。
So to do that, we're going to need to install Iron Ajax.
为此，我们将需要安装Iron Ajax。
We'll go back to our terminal.
我们将返回码头。
We'll split the panes.
我们将分为两个部分。
And we will bower install Iron Ajax, passing the save flag
并写凉亭安装Iron Ajax，传递保存信号
so it gets written to our elements bower JSON file.
将写入我们项目的Bower JSON文件中。
Now that is all good, we can go look
到目前为止一切都很好，我们可以回顾一下
at the element that was stubbed out for us by Yeoman.
项目被Yeoman截断了。
So this is gh-issues.html.
这些是gh-issues.html。
And if you browse around here, you'll
如果您浏览此处，
see there's a lot of boilerplate markup that it's stubbed out,
您会发现许多截断的标记样板标记
just as an example for what an element could look like.
作为元素可能是一个例子。
We'll ignore that for a second, and just
我们将跳过一秒钟，
go ahead and import Iron Ajax, as we
我们将继续导入Iron Ajax，
know we're going to use that, and I'll update
因此，我们将使用它，并更新我的商品说明。
So I'm going to say that this is an element for fetching issues
我将在这里写道，这是带来问题的要素
from GitHub, and then I can go through and delete
从GitHub删除
all of this extra markup that's inside of here.
所有其他编码都在这里。
So again, I don't really need any of this.
同样，我不需要任何这些。
It's just sort of example markup in case
这只是一个例子，以防万一
you haven't written an element before.
您之前没有写过任何东西。
It's good to read through just to see what's possible,
最好浏览一下，看看您能做什么。
but I want to strip it down to where I just
但我想将其删除
have this sort of very bare skeleton.
这种抽象结构。
Next I'm going to drop the iron-ajax tag
在下面，我将放置铁制ajax标签
inside of my template, and I'm going to configure it
在我的表单中，我将对其进行格式化
with a few attributes here.
在这里有一些功能。
So this auto attribute tells Iron Ajax to just
所以这里的auto属性告诉Iron Ajax
automatically fetch data.
自动获取数据
Any time it has a valid URL, it's just
只要有有效的网址，
going to go and get some data.
我继续获取一些数据。
This url attribute, as the name implies,
此url属性的名称表示，
is going to be where we go and get our data from.
指示我们将从何处获取数据。
When that data comes back, we're going
当您返回这些数据时，
to need to handle it as something.
我们需要将其视为某种东西。
So here we're saying handle it as JSON.
在这里，我们将把handle作为JSON编写。
I believe it also supports XML, and you could also
我认为它也支持XML，您也可以
tell it to fetch things as a document.
告诉他以文件形式带东西。
So for instance, if you were fetching an HTML file,
因此，例如，如果您要获取HTML文件，
you could say, hey, when that comes back
你可以说回来的时候
I want it treated as a document.
您要将其作为文档进行处理。
And then it also fires events.
活动也可以启动。
So there's a response event which we could listen to,
在这里，我们有一个响应事件，我们可以听
and we could have a handler that works with that.
我们可以放置一个与此处理器配合使用的处理器。
But instead of writing a bunch of JavaScript
而不是编写很多JavaScript
to handle the response that comes back,
为了处理我们的回应，
let's just go ahead and give it a URL.
我们将为其分配一个URL。
So I'm going to tell it to look at robdodson/chart-elements.
所以我告诉他回到robdodson / chart-elements。
That's the repo where we'll pull our data from.
这是我们将从中提取数据的存储库。
And I'm going to tell it to instead of handling that
我会告诉他而不是解决
in JavaScript, well just take the data that came back,
在JavaScript中，我们将获取返回的数据
which is represented as this last-response property,
显示为最后响应的属性，
and we'll create a scope variable for that called
我们将为其设计一个域变量
response.
反应。
Now, let's think about what's happened here
现在让我们考虑一下这里发生了什么
for just a second.
一秒钟。
I've got this one tag, and it basically represents GitHub.
我有这个标签，它基本上代表了GitHub
This is like a representation of the GitHub API.
这是GitHub API的演示。
I've configured it by saying this
我通过选择将其配置为
is where I'd like you to get data from,
我要从哪里获取数据
and then I've basically used a data binding to create sort
然后使用数据绑定来创建
of a declarative data provider.
元数据提供程序的种类。
So I don't really know the mechanics
我真的不知道机制
of how it is going and getting my data, nor do I care.
我并不关心它获取数据的方式。
Like, the implementation of how it's actually going and getting
我真的不在乎如何实现方法
the data I don't actually care about.
接收数据。
Instead, all I care about is that it goes here
相反，我所关心的是
and it gives me this data.
去拿给我这些数据。
And with this data binding, because it's
因为数据绑定是一种很好的强制性方法
nice and declarative, I can now hook onto it
通过它我可以链接到它
with different dom nodes, and they will stay in sync
通过不同的dom节点，它们将保持同步
with the data.
随着数据。
So this has removed the need for me to write a lot of JavaScript
因此您不再需要编写很多JavaScript
in my element.
在元素中。
Normally, I'd have to handle that response,
通常我必须解决这个问题
pick it apart, go find the different dom nodes that I want
对其进行分段，然后寻找不同的dom节点
to update with the new data.
用新数据更新。
Here we're just saying, hey, I've
在这里，我们只需要
got this nice declarative data provider,
获取此出色的元数据提供程序
and when that data comes back, all of my dom
当这些数据返回我所有的dom
nodes that bind to it will stay nice and in sync.
与之关联的所有dom节点都将保持正常并同步。
So pretty cool approach there.
这是一个很好的方法。
This is a representation of the response
这是回应
that we're going to get back from GitHub.
我们将从GitHub恢复。
You can see it's an array of objects.
您会看到它是一个对象数组
And the properties that I care about
我感兴趣的特征
are this one right here called html_url.
此处的名称是否为html_url。
So this is the actual URL to the GitHub issue.
这是GitHub问题的实际URL。
And then I also care about the title.
我也对标题感兴趣。
So this is what will display in our list of issues.
这将在我们的问题列表中显示。
So let's go back to our template here.
现在让我们回到我们的模型。
And because we've got this nice declarative data provider now,
而且因为我们有这个元数据提供者，
let's generate some dom for it to link up to.
让我们创建一些dom节点，以便可以链接它们。
So I'll create a template with a dom-repeat template,
所以我要用dom-repeat模型设计一个模型
and I'm going to give it an items attribute,
我会给他分配项目标签，
and we're going to link these two together.
我们将两者结合在一起。
So you can see this little linkage
这样你就可以看到链接
that we've created here.
我们在这里创建的。
We're saying the items should be linked to that response.
我们说项目应与这一回应联系起来。
So now that these are combined, this template
现在，结合它们的组合，该模型将尝试
is going to try to iterate over that collection,
在整个小组中重复
that array of objects.
并跨越这个对象矩阵。
So we can drop a div with an anchor inside of here,
我们可以在里面放一个带有锚点的div，
and we can bind to-- for every single item,
对于每个单独的项目
we can bind to its html_url and its title.
我们可以将其与html_url及其地址相关联。
So now we're just generating this sort
现在我们将创建
of list of anchor tags based on that response.
基于此响应的锚标记列表。
And this is pretty cool because, again, I
那很棒，因为你
didn't have to write a bunch of JavaScript to handle all this.
您无需编写很多JavaScript即可处理所有这些事情。
I just created this little linkage here.
我所做的就是创建这个小链接。
I've got this nice little declarative data provider.
我有这个很好的元数据提供程序。
And I'm just generating dom based
我只是创建一个dom锚
on the data that it returns.
根据数据返回。
So let's go look at the demo file
所以我们去演示文件
that I showed you earlier as part of our documentation.
稍后我会向您展示作为我们文档的一部分。
We're going to clean this up a little bit so that we
我们会稍微删除一下
can preview our tag.
所以我们可以查看标签
Again, Yeoman generates a bunch of boilerplate.
同样，Yeoman创建了一组样板。
And it's cool if you haven't seen it before,
如果您以前从未看过它，将会发现它很棒
but in our case, we're just going to delete it.
但就我们而言，我们将其删除。
We'll drop in the gh-issues tag.
我们将标记gh问题。
I'll blow this up a little bit so you
我会把它放在一边
can kind of see a bit better.
这样您可以更清楚地看到。
And, yeah, let's just preview this thing in Chrome.
现在，让我们在Chrome中对此进行回顾。
So we'll click on our Demo button,
我们将点击演示按钮，
and we'll see these are the two issues that
我们会发现两个问题
come back from that repo.
他们从这个仓库回来了。
I'll click on one and open it in a new tab,
我将单击其中之一，然后在新页面中将其打开。
just to verify that it came from Rob Dodson chart elements.
并验证它们是否来自Rob Dodson图表元素。
So, OK.
像这样
Yeah.
在这里，我们有一个活动的关键元素。
It's fetching data from the GitHub API, And.
它从GitHub API准备数据，
So far we haven't really written any JavaScript whatsoever.
到目前为止，我们根本没有编写任何JavaScript。
We're just fetching data.
我们只是准备数据。
We're generating dom based on that data.
我们基于该数据创建一个dom。
And that's kind of a cool flow, but let's see
那是一条好路，但是要看
if we can push this a little bit further and make this thing
如果我们可以继续
a bit more configurable.
并使其更具可配置性。
So if we go back and we look at our element's definition,
因此，如果我们回头看看元素定义。
you can see that I've hard coded the path here,
您可以看到我在此处为此路径添加了静态编码，
which is kind of a bummer, right?
哪个问题吧？
I want anybody to be able to use this tag.
我希望任何人都可以使用此标签。
And so what I can do is I can take the owner,
所以我能做的就是拿主人的名字，
and I can take the repo name, and I
取了仓库的名字
can make these configurable properties of this element.
我可以使它们成为此元素的可配置属性。
One called owner, and we're going to say that by default it
其中之一称为所有者，我们将其默认值
has the value of Polymer.
它具有“聚合物”的值。
Sure, why not?
为什么不呢
And we're also going to make it two-way bindable.
我们还将使它可以从两个方向连接。
So we'll say it fires change events when it changes.
因此，我们将使它们在更改时触发更改事件。
So we're saying it's notify:true.
在这里，我们将编写notify：true。
And we'll also create another property called repo.
我们还将创建另一个称为存储库的属性。
We'll also set that to Polymer, and this will also
我们还将其设置在Polymer上，它将
be two-way bindable.
两路可连接。
And lastly, I'm going to create a computed property called url,
最后，我将创建一个称为url的计算属性，
and what it's going to do is it's
她将要做的是
going to compute the values of owner and repo.
将计算所有者和仓库的价值。
It's going to-- So if either of these changes,
这样，如果其中之一被更改，
it's going to recompute the URL where
您的网址将重新计算
we're fetching from in GitHub.
我们从GitHub获取。
And we're going to stub out this method here for computeurl.
我们将在此处截断此方法以计算网址。
I'll say, hey, when we get owner and repo, what we should do
当我们拥有所有者和仓库时，我们要做的就是
is we should take that hard coded URL that we were working
我们将使用我们处理过的这个静态编码的URL
with before-- so let's just copy this--
在..之前，让我们复制一下
we'll drop it into an array, and we'll
并将其放入矩阵中
replace where it has the owner and repo right here,
我们将在这里替换所有者和仓库
we'll just replace with these two values
放置这两个值
that are being passed in.
哪些通过了。
So as someone is configured our tag,
因此，当有人配置我们的代码时，
they're passing in owner and repo.
它经过所有者和仓库
That's going to update this URL.
这将更新此URL。
So I'll pass those in, and then we're
所以我要通过，然后
just going to join the whole string with slashes
我们将仅通过斜杠条件组合整个字符串
to turn it back into a URL.
将其返回为URL格式。
And we'll say, hey, this is what Iron Ajax should bind to,
我们要说的是Iron Ajax应该绑定的东西，
this configurable computed URL now.
现在已计算出可配置的URL。
So let's switch back over to Chrome,
让我们回到Chrome，
now that we've got this set up, and we can go look at our demo.
现在我们已经设置好了，我们可以查看该演示了。
And see, now we're seeing all the issues
现在，我们从Polymer库中看到了所有问题。
We can actually open one of these
我们可以打开一个
and see, yep, organizations, Polymer, Polymer repo.
让我们看一下，这是组织，聚合物，聚合物回购。
But let's configure it a little bit more.
但是，让我们做得更好。
So now we can go and we can pass whatever owner and repo
现在我们可以走了，我们可以通过我们想要的任何所有者和仓库
we want, because we have these properties
因为我们有那些属性。
and we can pass them values as attributes.
我们可以将值作为属性传递。
So let's look at Polymer elements paper input.
因此，让我们看一下聚合物元素的输入。然后我们刷新页面。
Now we're looking at issues from paper input.
现在我们来看一下纸张输入中的问题。
So this is pretty cool.
这很酷。
Now anybody can use this tag to pull issues from GitHub,
现在，任何人都可以使用此标签从GitHub提取问题，
which is pretty awesome, right?
哪个很棒，对吗？
But I think we can actually take this a bit further.
但是我认为我们可以添加更多。
So just for funsies, let's take the demo that we're working on
让我们看一下我们正在做的演示
here and wrap it in an auto binding template,
在这里以自动链接的形式进行总结，
and this is going to let us use data bindings inside the space
这将使我们在空间内使用数据链接
without creating our own tag.
无需创建我们自己的标签。
And I'm just going to take owner and repo
我们将带走所有者和仓库
and make them bindable.
并使它们可连接。
So I'll create two text inputs.
因此，我将创建两个文本条目。
These are just native text inputs.
这些只是原始文本输入。
So one is going to bind to owner,
其中之一将与所有者相关联，
and one is going to be bound to this repo variable.
另一个将与此存储库变量关联。
And because we're creating data bindings on native elements,
由于我们基于原始元素创建数据链接，
notice that I'm using this sort of special double colon syntax.
请注意，我使用此冒号。
So this is sort of how Polymer allows you to set up
这就是聚合物允许您设置的方式
data bindings on native tags.
基于原始标签的数据链接。
Native tags, they fire their own events
原始标签发起自己的活动
when something has updated.
更新内容时。
In the case of the input element,
对于输入元素，
any time you have finished typing some text inside of it,
每当您在其中写完文字后，
it is going to fire a change event.
更改事件将被触发。
And so we're saying, hey, when you hear the change event,
所以我们说，当您发现更改发生时，
update the owner binding, right?
更新所有者链接，对吗？
Same with the repo binding.
库存链接也是如此。
So now we can go and I can replace
现在我们可以返回进行更换
these with those same scope variables, owner and repo.
这些与这些域，所有者和存储库变量一起使用
And now if we switch over to Chrome,
现在，如果我们回到克罗姆，
you'll see that at the bottom I've got these two text inputs.
您会看到下面有两个文本输入。
They are initially receiving the values
他们最初获得价值
that the gh-issues element put out.
由gh-issues元素发布。
So owner and repo are initially Polymer and Polymer.
因此，所有者和仓库是Polymer和Polymer。
But we can change these.
但是我们可以改变这一点。
So we can say, hey, this should be polymerelements,
我们可以说这应该是聚合元素，
and this should be, like, ironajax.
并具有讽刺意味。
And watch here.
看看这里。
All of the issues update, and that's
所有问题均已更新，
because we have that auto attribute on our Iron Ajax
这是因为我们在Iron Ajax元素中具有自动更新功能。
So we've given it some new values.
所以我们给了他新的价值观。
It recomputed the URL, it told Iron Ajax
重新计算了URL并告知Iron Ajax
to go fetch that new data, and that updated our dom for us.
为了获取这些新数据，并更新了我们的dom。
And again, we didn't need to write a bunch of JavaScript
同样，我们不需要编写很多JavaScript
to manage all of this flow, and that's, again,
要再次管理所有这些事情
the power of a nice declarative data provider
这就是出色的归纳数据提供者的力量
like Iron Ajax, which is pretty cool.
Iron Ajax，这非常好。
You can actually-- Yeah.
你可以..
You can open one of these up too,
打开这些问题之一
and you can see that-- verify that it's actually
你可以看到它，签出
pulling from polymerelements and Iron Ajax.
进行聚合物元素和Iron Ajax的提款
Now, another thing you may want to do when you work with Ajax
现在，在使用Ajax时，您可能还需要做其他事情
is pass along parameters.
它正在传递参数。
So you might be like, hey, I want
所以我们在这里说我要
to go to foo.com question mark q equals some value
通过去foo.com？ q =值
You pass along parameters as you're working with these URLs.
因此，您在使用URL链接时传递参数。
And if we look at the GitHub API,
如果我们看一下GitHub API，
you can see that there's a few parameters we could pass.
您可以发现我们可以传递一些参数。
One of them is state.
一种是状态。
So we could say, hey, give me all
所以我们可以说
of the issues for this repo, and maybe I
给我这个仓库的所有问题
want just the closed ones or just the open ones.
我可能只想看封闭或开放的问题。
So that's one parameter that we can use.
这是我们可以使用的参数之一。
Another one is this down here for page.
下面的页面还有另一个自定义参数。
It's a little hard to see, but we can actually
很难看到，但我们可以，
paginate our URL as well.
还拆分URL。
So we could be like, hey, I want page three of all of the closed
在这里，我可以请求所有已关闭问题的第三页。
Stuff like that, right?
这样的事情。
So let's go, and let's add that to our element as well.
现在，我们也将其添加到元素中。
We'll go back to our markup here,
我们将在这里返回编码。
and we can give iron-ajax this params attribute,
我们可以给这些参数赋予铁质ajax，
and you could give it this JSON encoded object,
您可以为其提供此加密的JSON对象，
and that could be how you pass along parameters.
这就是参数传递的方式。
So we could say "state" I want all the open issues,
因此，我们可以编写“状态”并询问所有未解决的问题。
and I want it to be page number 1.
我想成为第一页。
But again, where's the fun in that?
但是第二次，它的乐趣在哪里？
Let's make this configurable.
让我们使其可配置。
So much like we did with the URL,
就像我们对网址所做的一样
we can replace params with a computed value.
我们可以用计算值代替参数。
So I'm going to create a binding for options.
因此，我将创建一个指向选项的链接。
That's what we'll call our computed value.
这将是我们计算值的名称。
And we'll say that we want to create state and page
我们将说我们要创建“状态”页面和“页面”页面。
properties, and we will create a new computed value
我们将创建一个新的计算值
called options, which'll just compute state and page.
称为选项，它将计算状态和页面。
So any time those change, it is going
因此，如果随时更改其中任何一个，
to return a JSON object with whatever the state is
无论情况如何，您都将返回JSON对象
and whatever the page is.
无论页面如何。
So it's kind of a weird example, but you
这是一个奇怪的例子，
can see that it demonstrates how parameters work.
但是您可以看到它显示了参数的工作方式。
So now we can go back and we can create bindings for state
现在，我们可以返回并创建状态链接，
and page inside of our demo.
和演示中的页面。
And just like we did with owner and repo,
正如我们对所有者和仓库所做的那样。
I will create input fields for these as well.
我还将为这些属性创建输入字段。
So now when we swap back, if you look,
现在，当我们回去时，如果你看看这里
you can see again it's initially bound to Polymer, Polymer,
您会发现它们最初也与Polymer，Polymer，
it defaults to all of the open issues,
默认为所有未解决的问题
and it defaults to page one.
并设置在第一页上。
And so let's change that.
让我们改变它。
Let's say, hey, I want to see the closed issues in Polymer.
假设我要查看聚合物中的封闭问题，好的。
OK.
已更新。
I want to see page three of the closed issues in Polymer.
我想看看封闭聚合物问题的第三页，好的。
And I want to look at page three of the closed
我想看封闭问题的第三页
issues from maybe, like, paper input, and that works as well.
例如，从纸张输入的内部发生了这种情况。
And again, we can go back and we can open one of these,
同样，我们可以回过头来解决其中一个问题，
and we can verify it's a closed issue coming from paper input.
我们可以从纸张入口验证这是一个封闭的问题。
So pretty cool.
太好了
We've created now this pretty robust little element.
现在，我们已经创建了这个强大的小元素。
It does a lot of really fancy stuff.
它执行很多好事情。
It's entirely configurable.
它是完全可配置的。
The user can just go and live edit it,
用户可以直接对其进行编辑，
and they're getting all this data back,
它将恢复所有这些数据。
it's updating the dom, and we're not
它会更新dom，
having to write a bunch of JavaScript
我们不需要编写很多JavaScript
to manipulate the dom in any way, which is rad.
以任何方式处理dom。
So when should you use Iron Ajax?
如果什么时候可以使用Iron Ajax？
Well, that really depends on context.
好吧，这在很大程度上取决于上下文。
If you're in a situation where you've got,
你处于一个位置并且你有
like, 30 iron-ajax sprinkled throughout your element, then,
大约30个铁ajax散布在整个元素中，
yeah, maybe consider doing it with JavaScript instead.
您可能需要改用JavaScript。
But if you only need a simple data provider
但是如果您需要一个简单的数据提供者，
without a whole lot of fuss, then
没有很多细节
perhaps Iron Ajax is a good fit for your application.
Iron Ajax可能是您的应用程序的最佳选择。
We talked a lot about Iron Ajax today.
今天我们谈论了很多有关Iron Ajax的问题​​。
But I've actually only barely scratched the surface,
但是我只是吃了硬皮。
and so if you go over to the catalog,
因此，如果您转到目录，
you can see that there is this Iron Elements section.
在这里，您会找到铁元素部分。
You can go there and check out the docs for Iron Ajax.
您可以访问它并浏览Iron Ajax文档。
And there's a ton of things that this does.
这些元素可以做很多事情。
It does, you know, the full breadth
它解决了您可以做的一切
of what you can do in Ajax.
在Ajax中广泛使用。
So you can add body to it.
您可以向其添加结构。
You could change the method to post or put.
您可以更改书写或排版样式。
You can see all the various methods
您可以看到各种样式
that the element supports, the events that it fires,
由组件支持，它触发的事件等。
So definitely go read through the docs of Iron Ajax,
因此，去浏览Iron Ajax文档，
because there's a lot of power in this one little tag.
因为您可以用这个简单的标志做很多事情。
Also, little bit of shameless promotion here.
这里有一个简单的声明。
We just finished doing a big event
我们刚刚为大型活动做准备
in Amsterdam, which we're calling our Polymer Summit.
在阿姆斯特丹，我们称之为聚合物峰会。
I'll draw a little link here, so you
这里有一个简单的链接，
can click on that annotation to go to the actual website.
您可以单击该窗口转到实际位置。
It's a full day of talks and code labs
这将是一整天的演讲和软件学习软件
for you to check out to learn all things Polymer.
要了解有关聚合物的一切。
So you can go check out our playlist over here
您可以在此处转到我们的视频列表
on the Chrome Developers channel and see all of our videos.
在Chrome开发者频道上，观看所有视频。
You can also go to our code labs and maybe click
您还可以访问代码实验室
this as an annotation.
您可以在该窗口上单击。
Go check out all of our code labs.
浏览所有代码实验室程序。
And again, there's tons of stuff for you
同样，有很多事情
to play with if you're just getting started with Polymer,
如果您开始使用聚合物，则可以尝试一下，
or even if you're a bit of a Polymer pro.
或者即使您是专业人士，
There's probably something in here for you.
您会在这里找到适合您的东西。
So if you missed the Polymer Summit, go check that out.
如果您错过了聚合物会议，请转到此处。
That's it for today, folks.
朋友们，今天就这样。
If you've enjoyed this episode, consider
如果你喜欢那集
clicking that little Subscribe button down there
点击下面的共享按钮
Also, if you have questions for me,
如果您有任何疑问
you can leave them in the comments
您可以在评论中留下它们
or you can ping me on a social network of your choosing
或者您可以将其保留在您喜欢的任何社交媒体上
at #AskPolymer.
在#AskPolymer上。
As always, thank you so much for watching,
像往常一样谢谢你的收看
and I'll see you next time.
下集见。